Andrew Moses

Full Stack Web Developer focused on creating unique, accessible, and user-friendly applications. Experienced team lead with a demonstrated history of success in leadership within the financial services and healthcare industries. Lifelong learner with a continuous drive to broaden my skill set, take on challenges, and solve problems.

Tempe, Arizona
(480) 612-5250
andrewmosesdrive@gmail.com
GitHub
Portfolio

EXPERIENCE

DevCore/Quicken Loans — Trainer, Team Captain

2019 - PRESENT

Leads new team members through intensive training on all areas of knowledge related to their future careers. Mentors and coaches new trainers as they develop their training skills.

Donor Network of Arizona — *Lead Recovery Coordinator*

2011 - 2019

Directed teams of 3-5 individuals in highly adaptive and situations with heavy time restrictions. Trained new and existing staff in all clinical positions and medical record/suitability review via EMR.

PROJECTS

Management ERP — GitHub, Deployment

Full stack enterprise resource planning application built with three other developers using Node, Express-Handlebars, and Sequelize ORM. Deployed through Heroku.

Team Generator CLI — GitHub

Command line interface application for team template generation. Created with Node, Inquirer, and Jest for testing.

Fitness Tracker — <u>GitHub</u>, <u>Deployment</u>

Full stack application for creating, tracking, and logging workouts with persistence. Built with MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, and Node. Deployed via Heroku.

Central Management System — <u>GitHub</u>

Command line interface ERP application for organizational structuring. Following standard CRUD operations, this application was built with Node, MySQL, and Inquirer.

TOOLS/TECHNOLOGIES

React, AWS Amplify, JavaScript, Node, Express, HTML5, CSS3, Handlebars, MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, JawsDB, GraphQL, jQuery, Lodash, Materialize, Bootstrap, Webpack, Babel, PWA's

Visual Studio, Git, Slack, Chrome DevTools, NPM, Heroku, CRUD, Agile Methodology, Unit Testing

EDUCATION

University of Arizona — Full Stack Web Development Certificate

2019

Scottsdale Community College — Associates Degree

2016 - 2018